

Frontend Developer

+90 535 457 72 40

github.com/Spencehiko

## **Summary**

Passionate student of intriguing subjects.

Open to new ideas and willing to use my skills combined with well-thought projects.

Building CMSs and Websites since 2018.

Worked both in a start-up, a normal sized company and a global company. So I know every struggle, every challenge that companies face, no matter how big they are.

Looking forward to taking my current skills to upper levels and benefit both myself and the company I am working for.

# Work experience

## **Assistant Software Engineer**

06/2021 - NOW

Huawei

Currently I am working in Huawei as an assistant software engineer and mainly focused on frontend development. We developed several tools on Petal Maps with Vue.js, Typescript and HTML/CSS(LESS). Although we had a small team of developers, we managed to overcome tough obstacles on our way.

I won a Future Star Award at the end of 2021.

## **Junior Full Stack Web Developer**

12/2018 - 05/2021

Firmasoft Information Technologies

I was working as a Junior Full Stack Web Developer and we were building CMS with PHP, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery and MySQL. I learnt most of the things that I know right now while working in here about web technologies.

## **Junior Frontend Developer**

06/2018 - 11/2018

**Datapare Information Technologies** 

This was my first working experience. I learnt basics of HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript. I worked with Vue.js for not a long time but I know the basic expressions of it.

#### **Education**

**Graduate** 2016 - 2021

Istanbul Technical University

GPA: 2.97

## Skills

Vue.is

I have been working with Vue.js for my current company and also I am developing personal apps to improve myself. At work we use Vuex and in my personal projects I use Pinia with Composition API.

**TypeScript** 

I have been working with TypeScript implemented in Vue.js.

**PHP** 

I have been working with PHP for over 2 years and I have built several CMSs with it. I am familiar with OOP and API structures of PHP.

HTML5 & CSS3

For many years, I have worked with HTML and CSS. I have a really good understanding of the correlation between them and I can code a design for the web page easily. I know LESS too.

**Javascript** 

I have been working on this subject for over 4 years and I have built several apps with it.

MySQL

I have the knowledge of basic queries and data structures of MySQL.

**Github** 

I have simple knowledge of Git commands. (push, pull, merge etc.) I have been using Sourcetree to visualize these actions, but I can use them on command line as well.

**Testing Tools** 

I used Jest for unit testing and Cypress for end-to-end testing. I have the basic knowledge of them.

MATLAB/ C/ C++

I have enrolled in this course at my college and passed it with an A+. No further experiences.

#### **Skills**

**English** 

I can explain myself confidently in any situation fluently.

Chinese

I am a beginner in Chinese and I really find it intriguing.

#### **Hobbies**

- Video Games
- Teaching Mathematics and Geometry
- Photography
- Books (Sci-Fi, Historical, War, Science)
- Sports

### References

Serkan Uz - CEO and Founder of Datapare Information Technologies

serkanuz@datapare.com

Mustafa Tunç - CEO and Founder of Firmasoft Information Technologies

mustafatunc@firmasoft.com

Salih Kesepara - Team Leader of Petal Maps Frontend Team at Huawei R&D

salih.kesepara@huawei.com